onemorepost.com 2018-01-29

# TheMindCircle

**Privacy Policy**

At themindcircle.com, we know that your personal information’s privacy is very important. Below are the kinds of personal information we collect and receive when you are visiting our site, and how we protect your information. Unlike other companies, we also don’t sell your personal information to the 3rd parties.

 **Web Beacons and Cookies**

We use cookies when storing information including your personal preferences once you visited our website. This include showing a popup window once when visiting or logging in to access some of our site’s features like forums.

We also make use of 3rd party advertisements to support our website. Some of these third parties are using technology like web beacons and cookies when advertising on our website that will also send such advertisers including Google through Google AdSense program information including your web browser, ISP, IP address and some software like Flash. Generally, we use this for geotargeting purposes, which show ads based on the particular websites visited.

 **Log Files**

Like majority of websites out there, we use and collect data contained in the log files. The information in our log files include IP address, ISP, browser, time you visited the site and which pages you have visited when browsing our website.

 **Links**

Our website contains different links to several sites. This only means that we aren’t responsible for the privacy measures of some sites. We encourage each of our users to be aware once they leave our website and to read privacy statements of every website that collects personal information. Our privacy statement only applies to our own website.

 **Advertisers**

As mentioned earlier, we are using 3rd party advertising companies to serve advertisements on our website. Such companies can use information regarding your visits to this and some websites to give ads about services and goods that can give you interests. We don’t have access to these details. If you need more information about such practices and to determine your choices about not having information used by such companies, you may check out for our updates.

 **Changes to Our Privacy Policy Statement**

While we don’t intent to make some changes to our privacy statement often, we have the right to make some changes on out policy any time. If our information practices were changed in the future, we will change our statement regarding user’s privacy instantly. If you are a bit worried about the how the information will be used, you must check back at the website regularly.

 **Contact Us**

If you need more information regarding the information we collect from our users and how we protect them, please don’t hesitate to send us an email and we will give you the answers you need for your questions.

contact@themindcircle.com
